<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Python and R</title>
      <link>/blog/python-and-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/python-and-r/</guid>
      <description>The reticulate package let’s R and python work together! Simply define something in the R code chunk
library(reticulate) so&amp;lt;- &amp;quot;Stay Healthy&amp;quot; then define something in the python code chunk. After you print out the result you can show your message!
cool=&amp;quot;Everyone&amp;quot; print(r.so,cool)  These are hard times for many people so here are some memes to brighten your day!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neha&#39;s Project Topics</title>
      <link>/blog/neha/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/neha/</guid>
      <description>Project Topics
I decided to analyze traffic data for my projects because driving is something most of us can relate to. Driving is a daily activity that most of us do not think about when we are doing it but there are many things that can subconsciously contribute to how we drive. I chose to analyze data regarding the presence of traffic cameras, as well as laws we are aware of to see if it had any effect on how safe people drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects Here are some projects I have recently completed:
  Exploratory Data Analysis with Tidyverse Tools
  Modeling, Testing, and Classification
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1</title>
      <link>/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project1/</guid>
      <description>Neha Momin nbm522
Introduction The first dataset is bad_drivers and it contains information on the number of drivers involved in a fatal collision per billion miles, the percent of drivers involved in a collision while speeding, percent of drivers in a collision that were alcohol impaired, the percent of drivers that were not distracted during the collision, the percent of drivers in a collision with no previous accidents, the average insurance premiums by state, and the losses incurred by the insurance companies for collisions per insured driver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2</title>
      <link>/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2/</guid>
      <description>Neha Momin nbm522
R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
When you click the Knit button a document will be generated that includes both content as well as the output of any embedded R code chunks within the document. You can embed an R code chunk like this:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>